http://www.chatopus.com/privacy_policy.html

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Chatopus collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.chatopus.com website ("Site") and its products ("Products").
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site/Products. Users may visit our Site and use some of our Products anonymously. Products that require identification will be explicitly stated in their corresponding Product pages. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from using some of the Products offered.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site and Products. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, geographical locations, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site and Products, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Chatopus may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve our Site/Products. We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site/Products that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site/Products. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site/Products, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Chatopus has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using our Site/Products, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site/Products. Your continued use of the Site/Products following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Chatopus, www.chatopus.com, support@chatopus.com
This document was last updated on Sep 28, 2013.
© 2012-2014 Chatopus. All rights reserved.
Design by NodeThirtyThree Design
